
const quizArr = [
    {
      id: 1,
        question: "Muslims will often write the initials P.B.U.H. after the name of a prophet. What does this mean?",
        options: {
          A: "Please be utterly happy",
          B: "Peace be upon him",
          C: "Peace be under heaven",
          D: "Peace be up high",
        },
        answer: "B",  
      },
      {
         id: 2,	
        question: "In which direction do Muslims face when praying?",
        "options": {
          A: "Towards Mecca",
          B: "Towards Istanbul",
          C: "Towards Rome",
          D: "Towards Jerusalem",
        },
        answer: "A",
      },
      {
         id: 3,   	
         question: "The name Islam comes from the word 'Salaam', which means .......",
         options: {
          A: "love",
          B: "freedom",
          C: "peace",
          D: "justice",
        },
        "answer": "C",
      },
      {
        id: 4,  
        question: "The holy month of prayer, fasting and pilgrimage is known as .......",
        options: { 
         A: "Spring",
         B: "Eid",
         C: "Ramadan",
         D: "Shahadah",
        },
        answer: "C",
      },
      {
        id: 5,  
        question: "How many times a day should Muslims pray?",
        options: {
        A: "Once",
        B: "Twice",
        C: "Four times",
        D: "Five times"
        },
        answer: "D",
      },
      { 
        id: 6,
        question: "Which of the following is NOT a holy and sacred book in Islam?",
        options: {
         A: "The Koran",
         B: "The Psalms",
         C: "The Bible",
         D: "De Anima"
        },
        answer: "D",
      },
       {
        id: 7,    	
        question: "Where do Muslims go to worship?",
        options: {
          A: "temple",
          B: "church",
          C: "synagogue",
          D: "mosque",
        },
        answer: "D",
        
      },
      { 
        id: 8,
        question: "How many pillars of Islam are there?",
        options: {
         A: "Four",
         B: "Five",
         C: "Eight",
         D: "Ten",
        },
        answer: "B",
        
      },
      { 
        id: 9,  
        question: "One of the pillars of Islam is Salah, which means .......",
        options: {
         A: "prayer",
         B: "fasting",
         C: "giving to charity",
         D: "pilgrimage"
         },  
        answer: "A",
        
      },
      {
         id: 10, 
         question: "What is the name for the pilgrimage to Mecca which all faithful Muslims must try to undertake at least once?",
         options: {
         A: "Shahadah",
         B: "Salah",
         C: "Hajj",
         D:  "Zakah",
        },
        answer: "C",
      },
      {	
        id: 11, 
      question: "Name 3 Surahs that begins with meem?",
      options: {			
      A: "Mur-salat, Maryam,  Muhammad",   
      B: "Al-nami, IQra, The Samad",
      C: "Albaqara, Al-emran, Alfalag",
      D: "Zakah",
      },
      answer: "A",
  },
  {
  id: 12, 
  question: "3 Acts which Allah Loves?",
  options: {
      A: "Feeding the poor, the orphan and Praying", 
      B: "Working, playing, laughing", 
      C: "been famous, wining trophies",
       D:  "Zakah",
          },
          answer: "A",
  },
  {
  id: 13, 
  question: "things Allah Hates?",
  options: {
  
      A: "helpful person",
      B: "Hypocrites, laying, Shaytan",
      C: "Prayer", 
      D:  "Zakah",
      }, 
      answer: "B",
  },
  {
  id: 14, 
  question: "Name three animals haram to eat?", 
  options: {
  
      A: "Chicken, COW, Fish", 
      B: "goats, Birds, Camel",
      C: "Pig, Monkey ,Dog",
      D:  "Zakah",
      }, 
      answer: "C",
  },
  {
  id: 15, 
  question: "What does all prophets have in common",
  options: {
  
      A: "They Were Kings", 
      B: "They were all Shepherds",
      C: "They were carpenters",
      D:  "Zakah",
      }, 
      answer: "B",
  },
  {
  id: 16, 
  question: "Name 3 Blessed days throughout the year?",
  options: {
  
      A: "Laylat Asabt, Alahad, Alethnien", 
      B: "Laylat Athlatha, Alarbaa, Alkahmis",
      C: "Laylatul Qadr, Fridays, Eid al-Fitr",
      D:  "Zakah",
      }, 
      answer: "C",
  },
  {
  id: 17, 
  question: "Who was the grandfather of prophet yusuf(AS)?",
  options: {
  
      A: "Ishaq (AS)", 
      B: "Isah (AS)",
      C: "Mussa (AS)",
      D:  "Zakah",
      }, 
      answer: "A",
  },
  {
  id: 18, 
  question: "Which Quranic verses were revealed to the prophet SAW when magic had been done on him?",
  options: {
  
      A: "Surah Altakathur, Surah Alkaferoon, Surah Albiana", 
      B: "Surah Al-Nas, Surah Al-Falarq",
      C: "Surah Al-Masad, Surah Alrahman",
      D:  "Zakah",
      }, 
      answer: "B",
  },
  {
  id: 19, 
  question: "Name the best night and best day?",
  options: {
  
      A: "Laylatull Alahad, Laylatull khamis", 
      B: "Laylatull Althalatha, Jumaa ",
      C: "Laylatull Qadr, Arafa",
      D:  "Zakah",
      }, 
      answer: "C",
  },
  {
  id: 20, 
  question: "When are we closest to Allah (SWT)?",
  options: {
  
      A: "Sujood (Prostration)", 
      B: "Rukoo",
      C: "Iqama",
      D:  "Zakah",
      }, 
      answer: "A",
  },
  ];
